Hello friends my name is Anil Rajput
and today I am presenting to you a
very good
Mediclaim scheme launched by which the name is SEND MONEY has a
very good feature in it watch this entire
video if you like this video then subscribe to my
YouTube channel
subscribe and yes
definitely do Appointed Subscribe
means
Appointed
Subscribe
secondly if I am employed for any work
then does my policy have non
medical expenses and non medical expenses
which are called benefits to the consumer like
Mar's Club Pet in this way
six and a half inch back cover will be covered so youth
must subscribe to the channel that
if I take my policy then
you need maternity benefit I can get
maternity benefit under this policy
before taking the policy if I have
any one of the diseases A B C D then you
subscribe if you
want any of them first then I do not know
that this policy provides Restore Benefits
now this to validate the stock limit in rain
Zulu video to subscribe to me
now let's talk in details of the plan
before that a little about the company  Let's find out what
Manipal Signal Company is. This
Manipal Group, which is an education system company that has been
working for many years, has appointed two companies. The
company has a claim
settlement ratio of 9.6 in 2 hours. More than
250 people are
talking about this company's products. If you start learning, let me tell you one thing
that this Manipal Group is a
225 year old group and it
works in more than 30 countries and
along with this, 10 customers have subscribed to this company so far. The
company is one of the top 500
companies in the world. You can subscribe to that table and
subscribe. So, if
our country's company is
subscribing to this company,
then comment below, what percentage of its political support is it getting
and the company is in the grip of the
world. This year, I have
put a small list of Indian companies, see at number 12, it is the
top sex in the world.
Now let's talk about the plan. After the plan, an
observer has been
appointed for the people in the helpline. Let's
talk about those who do not have any health issues.
For them, on two glasses, Raghavendra has appointed his
professional life products.  Let's
start with the health
products app,
in this option you
can see insurance cover ranging from four lakhs to one crore,
here you will be seeing five unique features,
switch option by restoration committee, if you
subscribe for example, it does
not take time, then
you can
complete the subscription
in one month, the
prime example, in this policy you
get the benefit of ambulance, now you will
say that
what is the difference in this and the ambulance of other companies, other companies
provide ambulance, so
here he tries to explain to you that
he
subscribed and there the
company sends the
customer to the
hospital and
subscribes, now he gets admitted in the hospital
for treatment,
but in this matter
you had subscribed for
full ₹10, whatever comes to your mind when you get admitted in the special, it will
not score, it is very good
and unlimited restoration benefits,
in this policy you get the benefit of restoration,
restoration means that you
took a policy of ten lakhs, fell ill, did not use it, then
when will you get back to
school, then arrest the companies and
subscribe and you will get it again  Wake up to ₹10
Now the school and the company in this company
first of all is rich
and secondly subscribe subscribe subscribe
now
keep this school and if
unfortunately he gets cancer then
definitely he will go back for treatment
and the disease is also the same then also you will get the
restored Lakshmi water but
if it is any other company and in this the same person
and discovery is not done then they say that
brother the sample is not coming, that person is
sick and he is the giver of the disease also then we do
not have the benefit of restoration but
under this plan if any person gets
sick then when did you get the registration
prime cumulative bonus
that this bonus in most of the other companies plan is
given to him so
now you will say that
appointment so if
you
subscribe 250
grams of paneer
and
subscribe
definitely subscribe
and
subscribe
subscribe so
what happens in other areas of your network insurance company that like
guava
appointed
subscribe for you but here there is nothing like this
you
appointed
subscribe have been
looted
now what remains in this is that if the person who
proposed in Arghya policy meets with an accident  If it is
reasonable then you have to subscribe
as you can see in this picture, the
year has started, make a quality purchase, then the
next one which you do not have but the
appointed chairman,
now the
second part of the medical hospital till the school is
subscribed,
now let's talk about optional packages and optional
cover and affected Gautam Adani,
like take a connection from your TV in between, that
I have
taken, there subscribe to the option
appointed
channel
and
subscribe, if India's match is going on then
I want a support channel, then
subscribe to the channel, so here and subscribe,
what will happen in Dance Plus, if your
search limit is exhausted, you will also
get the best of the best in that private hospital, secondly the maternity benefit
which is the insurance cover
subscribed is maximum 1 lakh rupees,
in this policy you will also get maternity benefit
which is 10 percent of your insurance
or ₹1000 which is maximum, you will get it,
thirdly is
help maintenance benefit which is available up to ₹3
in a year,
this means that if you have consulted the appointed doctor
then all these  I have also given you this
second
subscription so that it does
not get lost, then
definitely subscribe to this,
subscribe to the channel, you have to do the subscription, you have to
fold the critical illness
and keep selecting the deductible of 25000, that is,
you said that you will take it up to 25 thousand, then
I will not plan it in the company, I will do it
myself, so yours, subscribe to the media,
it depends on your wish, you
can find your text message, till now I
understood that there is more talk of pro helpline, so in this there are
so many benefits on just one,
you should
subscribe and
subscribe to that,
hey, Indian people
like this, who said that they will
get a discount, so if you take a family floater policy,
then you will get a 20% discount,
if you subscribe for Dausa district despite a long time
and
if you do your study,
if you
subscribe up
to 240,
talk about the basic features of this policy that
in wars, children of 3 months, children of 90 to
18 years, any person who
subscribes,
then subscribe,
subscribe
[music] you
can subscribe  It is
covered up to the maximum,
you
can take power up to 111 crores by doing insurance cover for Chawla, there
is an advantage plan, that will start from Garlic 5 lakhs,
policy offer one year, dhoti,
quality, disturbance,
relax,
subscribe, my channel does
not need to be subscribed, but on this channel,
you have the
treatment policy in the screen joint,
but if you go and get treatment
in the city of the zone, then we will need to comment on the 10 button,
okay, in this way you
can add it here by making the payment, now let's talk,
waiting,
waiting update appears
[music]
subscribe,
subscribe, if you are related to this, then for this the
government has a commission,
subscribe and
subscribe, now here
I am presenting some samples for you, according to your need, according to
what your need is,
you can join your insurance policy or
health policy yourself,
so here all the benefits of the product,
subscribe and subscribe
and subscribe,
now
subscribe to the school relaxation,
subscribe to the channel, if
you want worldwide emergency with
proper recovery, then you  What to take
part plus freedom from British rule was
but now you want a war of numbers, if you
want a non-medical app,
subscribe if you
can subscribe
and the
sum of appointment is
not
subscribe
plus plus
subscribe and till what time should I gift then
you can design your own plant accordingly,
now coming to the pro is crime active, this
means that if a customer already has a
problem of diabetes, obesity, soul, blood pressure, cholesterol, then
this option is available for them which is known as active option,
that customer can also take
that all my things can be seen on the news plate
here, there will be
a limit with what will be received, if you
subscribe to insurance and up to ₹5000
and if you
already have this disease, then click on the subscribe button, let's
talk about this subscribe to annual health checkup, if
you have the product of the
young generation, you
can understand in the list, then you
subscribe to this
channel, subscribe
means admission in school, do
not forget to subscribe to my channel and
subscribe and option  You will get it and you
can update it by meeting which ones, I have already
explained this, if you
take activation then you will get the benefit of Pipri in it, that
means infection benefit, you will
not get any voice mail address of the appointee
and if you have not subscribed for this then
please
subscribe, if you have subscribed to our channel then I
hope you liked this video, liked
this plan,
liked its features, the company is very
good, it is a 2 and a quarter year old company,
Question Phase is at number five
in the area of ​​no. 6%, they give the list within 2 hours
and both the premium and teachers
are excellent, if you want to
subscribe to this and need some information then you
can call me, if you want from me then you
can WhatsApp me my mobile number, that was
joint so much, please like, share and
subscribe my YouTube channel for a day